<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Cooking Expanded - Haute</name>
	<author>Sarg Bjornson, Oskar Potocki</author>
	<supportedVersions>

		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VCookE</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Cooking Expanded</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl></steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaCookingExpanded</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>VanillaExpanded.VCookE</li>
	</loadAfter>
  
	
		
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VCookEHaute</packageId>
	
	<description>Vanilla Cooking Expanded - Haute Module is a new addition to the Vanilla Cooking Expanded arsenal, utilising the various mechanics added by Vanilla Cooking Expanded mod. In Haute Meals, players will gain access to a brand new cooking station called electric haute section that will be utilised in creating the most exquisite of dishes, eclipsing even gourmet meals.
	
"Haute Meal" or "Haute Cuisine" is a perfect tier above Gourmet, fitting naturally into a hierarchy of meal quality. "Haute" comes from haute cuisine, which refers to the pinnacle of refined, meticulously prepared, and artistically presented food—often associated with Michelin-star restaurants, aristocratic dining, or even futuristic culinary innovations.

It conveys extreme attention to detail, rare ingredients, and a level of craftsmanship beyond mere "gourmet."

Haute meals take extremely long to make - they are the artworks of culinary arts. They often take a better part of the day to cook, and can only really be cooked efficiently by the real culinary masters - level 20 cooks.

Haute meals are the biggest waste of resources. They not only waste the time, but they also waste the nutrition in a never-seen-before ways. Realistically, only the most advanced and luxurious colonies will be cooking the haute meals.

Haute meals share a lot of similarities with art - they have quality, and depending on the quality, they will have different effects. They also have art descriptions - except it’s a dish description. These descriptions will generate to talk in detail about ingredients used and the flavor profiles they create, as well as what methods were used to achieve such a dish.

Haute meals provide the strongest mood buff when eaten - and the best part is, the mood thought is a unique mood thought for the individual dish, and eating several of these dishes will add up as individual mood thoughts. This means that a colonist might have three different mood thoughts from three different haute dishes they ate.

Additionally, haute dishes also create positive memories for other colonists who were there for the experience.

It’s probably not a meal you want to feed your entire colony with, but it’s something you can aspire to make for those special moments around your colony!
</description>
</ModMetaData>